Guide to the Actors' Fund of America Records WAG.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Fundraising Activities, 1886-2002; 183462
  - Subseries V:B: Benefits and Fairs, 1886-2002., 183609
    - Last of the Red Hot Lovers, Mar 1, 1970; 183858 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Private Lives, Mar 15, 1970; 183857 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Canterbury Tales, Apr 5, 1970; 183856 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Hair, Apr 12, 1970; 183855 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Harvey, Apr 26, 1970; 183854 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Coco, May 7, 1970; 183853 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Applause, Sep 27, 1970; 183852 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Hello, Dolly!, Oct 18, 1970; 183851 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Company, Nov 8, 1970; 183850 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Conduct Unbecoming, Dec 6, 1970; 183849 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Two by Two, Jan 3, 1971; 183848 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Rothschilds, Jan 17, 1971; 183847 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Sleuth, Jan 24, 1971; 183846 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Home, Feb 7, 1971; 183845 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - No, No, Nanette, Mar 14, 1971; 183844 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Design for Living, Apr 18, 1971; 183843 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - School for Wives, Apr 25, 1971; 183842 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Hair, May 17, 1971; 183841 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Follies, Oct 10, 1971; 183840 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Company, Oct 17, 1971; 183839 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Jesus Christ Superstar, Jan 9, 1972; 183838 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Sleuth, Jan 23, 1972; 183837 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Lenny, Jan 30, 1972; 183836 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Prisoner of Second Avenue, Feb 6, 1972; 183835 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Twigs, Feb 20, 1972; 183834 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Two Gentlemen of Verona, Mar 5, 1972; 183833 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Vivat! Vivat Regina!, Apr 9, 1972; 183832 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Purlie, Apr 23, 1972; 183831 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Sleuth, Apr 24, 1972; 183830 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Applause, Jun 11, 1972; 183829 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Follies, Jul 18, 1972; 183828 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Follies, Jul 21, 1972; 183827 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Follies, Jul 22, 1972; 183826 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - No, No, Nanette, Oct 3, 1972; 183825 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - That Championship Season, Nov 12, 1972; 183824 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Butley, Jan 14, 1973; 183823 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Grease, Feb 4, 1973; 183822 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Prisoner of Second Avenue, Feb 4, 1973; 183821 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Pippin, Mar 4, 1973; 183820 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Sunshine Boys, Mar 18, 1973; 183819 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Benefit Program: Auction, Apr 12, 1973; 183818 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Fishing Touches, Apr 15, 1973; 183817 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Changing Room, Apr 29, 1973; 183816 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Little Night Music, Jun 3, 1973; 183815 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Uncle Vanya, Jul 19, 1973; 183814 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Grease, Oct 28, 1973; 183813 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Bette Midler, Dec 23, 1973; 183812 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Liza, Jan 25, 1974; 183811 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Good Evening, Jan 27, 1974; 183810 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Good Doctor, Feb 10, 1974; 183809 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Moon for the Misbegotten, Mar 28, 1974; 183808 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Time for the Cuckoo, Apr 28, 1974; 183807 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Noel Coward in Two Keys, May 2, 1974; 183806 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Over Here, May 30, 1974; 183805 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Magic Show, Oct 27, 1974; 183804 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, Nov 24, 1974; 183803 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Gypsy, Dec 1, 1974; 183802 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Absurd Person Singular, Jan 12, 1975; 183801 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Sherlock Holmes, Jan 23, 1975; 183800 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Equus, Jun 26, 1975; 183799 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - In Praise of Love, Mar 2, 1975; 183798 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Doll's House, Mar 23, 1975; 183797 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Boys from Syracuse, Apr 28, 1975; 183796 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Same Time Next Year, Jun 8, 1975; 183795 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Chorus Line, Nov 2, 1975; 183794 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Wiz, Dec 7, 1975; 183793 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Chicago, Feb 22, 1976; 183792 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Royal Family, Mar 7, 1976; 183791 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Very Good Eddie, Mar 21, 1976; 183790 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Equus, May 2, 1976; 183789 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Chorus Line, Aug 16, 1976; 183788 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - My Fair Lady, Aug 29, 1976; 183787 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - California Suite, Sep 12, 1976; 183786 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Wiz, Oct 17, 1976; 183785 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Bubbling Brown Sugar, Oct 18, 1976; 183784 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Same Time, Next Year, Dec 26, 1976; 183783 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Guys and Dolls, Jan 2, 1977; 183782 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Waiting for Godot, Feb 28, 1977; 183781 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Chorus Line, Apr 17, 1977; 183780 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Annie, Sep 25, 1977; 183779 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Side by Side by Sondheim, Oct 23, 1977; 183778 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - King and I, Dec 18, 1977; 183777 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Dracula, Jan 8, 1978; 183776 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Gin Game, Jan 22, 1978; 183775 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Grease, Feb 20, 1978; 183774 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Touch of the Poet, Feb 26, 1978; 183773 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Chorus Line, Feb 26, 1978; 183772 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Hello, Dolly!, Mar 5, 1978; 183771 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Chapter Two, Mar 19, 1978; 183770 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Cold Storage, Mar 26, 1978; 183769 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Night of 100 Stars, Feb 14, 1982; 183768 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Night of 100 Stars: Board of Advisors, Feb 14, 1982; 183767 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Night of 100 Stars, Clippings, Feb 14, 1982; 183766 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Night of 100 Stars, Clippings (II), Feb 14, 1982; 183765 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Night of 100 Stars, Correspondence, Feb 14, 1982; 183764 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Night of 100 Stars, Playbill, Feb 14, 1982; 183763 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Night of 100 Stars: Quilt, Feb 14, 1982; 183762 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Night of 100 Stars: Reagan, Ronald, 1981; 183761 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Night of 100 Stars: Roger and Cowan Inc., Publicity, Feb 14, 1982; 183760 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Evite, Apr 18, 1982; 183759 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Dream Girls, Jun 27, 1982; 183758 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Nine, Sep 12, 1982; 183757 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Cats, Oct 5, 1982; 183756 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - 42nd Street, Nov 1982; 183755 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Cats, Feb 6, 1983; 183754 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Parade of Stars, May 2, 1983; 183753 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - You Can't Take It with You, Jul 17, 1983; 183752 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Dream Girls, Aug 29, 1983; 183751 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Brighton Beach Memories, Oct 30, 1983; 183750 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - La Cage Aux Folles, Nov 6, 1983; 183749 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - On Your Toes, Nov 20, 1983; 183748 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Torch Song Trilogy, Jan 23, 1984; 183747 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Rink, Jun 24, 1984; 183746 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Hurly Burly, Sep 23, 1984; 183745 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Harrigan 'n Hart, Jan 31, 1985; 183744 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Night of 100 Stars II, Feb 17, 1985; 183743 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Night of 100 Stars II: Clippings, Feb 17, 1985; 183742 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Night of 100 Stars II: Dinner, Feb 17, 1985; 183741 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Night of 100 Stars II: Roger and Cowen Inc, Publicity, Feb 17, 1985; 183740 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Night of 100 Stars II: Thank You Ad, Feb 17, 1985; 183739 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Night of Unsung Stars, Jun 3, 1985; 183738 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Biloxi Blues, Jun 23, 1985; 183737 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Best of the Best, Nov 3, 1985; 183736 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Only the Best Gala, Macy's, Nov 13, 1985; 183735 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Bridge to Broadway (Harms Plaza Theatre), Nov 18, 1985; 183734 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Chorus Line, Movie Premiere, Dec 9, 1985; 183733 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Chorus Line, Movie Premiere: Press, 1985; 183732 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Shear Madness, Apr 1, 1986; 183731 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - L.A. Stage Company Special Event, Jun 16, 1986; 183730 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Legends, Jul 1986; 183729 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Liberty State Park, NJ: Liberty Week, Jul 1986; 183728 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Producers Guild: New York International Film and Festival Awards Benefit, Nov 1, 1986; 183727 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Ginger Man Event, Dec 18, 1986; 183726 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Break A Leg Award Presentation, Jun 13, 1987; 183725 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Benefit Show, Jun 13, 1987; 183724 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Happy Birthday, Mr. Abbott (George Abbott 100th Birthday), Jun 22, 1987; 183723 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Happy Birthday, Mr. Abbott (George Abbott 100th Birthday): Publicity, 1987; 183722 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Career Transition for Dancers: Art Gala and Auction, Sep 21, 1987; 183721 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Starlight Express, Sep 23, 1987; 183720 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Capital Salute to the Entertainment World, Oct 5, 1987; 183719 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Shear Madness, Nov 5, 1987; 183718 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - For Me and My Girl, Jan 1988; 183717 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Christmas Carol, Dec 12, 1988; 183716 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Christmas Carol: Clippings, Dec 12, 1988; 183715 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Christmas Carol: Correspondence, Dec 12, 1988; 183714 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Christmas Carol: Correspondence, Thank You Notes, Dec 1988; 183713 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Christmas Carol: Invitations, Dec 12, 1988; 183712 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Christmas Carol: Invitations, Corporate, Dec 12, 1988; 183711 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Christmas Carol: Planning, Dec 12, 1988; 183710 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Christmas Carol: Publicity, Dec 12, 1988; 183709 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Jerome Robbins' Broadway, Mar 27, 1989; 183708 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Dennis Collado's Fund Raiser, May 1989-Jun 1989; 183707 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Phantom of the Opera, Aug 27, 1989; 183706 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Takarazuka, Oct 25, 1989-Oct 29, 1989; 183705 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Christmas Carol, Dec 11, 1989; 183704 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Christmas Carol: Program (signed), Dec 11, 1989; 183703 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Advertisement, May 5, 1990; 183702 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Artiste and Craft Guilds Committee, May 5, 1990; 183701 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Celebrities, May 5, 1990; 183700 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Correspondence, May 5, 1990; 183699 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Correspondence, May 5, 1990; 183698 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Diamond Information Center, Promotion, May 5, 1990; 183697 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Dinners and Parties, May 5, 1990; 183696 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Executive Committee, May 5, 1990; 183695 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: IATSE Boycott, May 5, 1990; 183694 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Invitation, May 5, 1990; 183693 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Planning, May 5, 1990; 183692 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Play Bill, May 5, 1990; 183691 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Play Bill, May 5, 1990; 183690 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Press Clippings, May 5, 1990; 183689 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Press Clippings (II), May 5, 1990; 183688 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Press Kit, May 5, 1990; 183687 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Performance Schedules, May 5, 1990; 183686 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Raffle (Noel Coward's Mercedes), May 5, 1990; 183685 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Reports, Profits, May 5, 1990; 183684 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Sales, May 5, 1990; 183683 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Script, May 5, 1990; 183682 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Stewart, Jimmy, May 5, 1990; 183681 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Chorus Lin e: Press Kit, Mar 31, 1990; 183680 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Phantom of the Opera, Jan 21, 1991; 183679 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - City of Angels, Feb 17, 1991; 183678 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Les Miserables, Apr 3, 1991; 183677 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Candida, Apr 7, 1991; 183676 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Six Degrees of Separation, Apr 28, 1991; 183675 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Lost in Yonkers, Jun 16, 1991; 183674 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Phantom of the Opera, Jun 17, 1991; 183673 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Madame Butterfly, Sep 8, 1991; 183672 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Phantom of the Opera, Sep 22, 1991; 183671 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Sara fina!, Sep 22, 1991; 183670 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Miss Saigon, Sep 27, 1991; 183669 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Nick and Nora, Oct 8, 1991; 183668 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Secret Garden, Oct 13, 1991; 183667 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Bon Appetit, Nov 11, 1991; 183666 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Christmas Carol, Dec 10, 1990; 183665 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Christmas Carol, Dec 16, 1991; 183664 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Christmas Carol: Correspondence, Dec 16, 1991; 183663 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Christmas Carol: Dinner, Dec 16, 1991; 183662 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Christmas Carol: Invitation and Contributions Lists, Dec 16, 1991; 183661 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Christmas Carol: Invitation Ideas, Artwork, Dec 16, 1991; 183660 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Christmas Carol: Planning, Dec 16, 1991; 183659 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Christmas Carol: Playbill, Dec 16, 1991; 183658 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Christmas Carol: Publicity, Dec 16, 1991; 183657 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Christmas Carol: Script, Dec 16, 1991; 183656 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Christmas Carol, Dec 19, 1991; 183655 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Most Happy Fella, Apr 12, 1992; 183654 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - CATS, Apr 19, 1992; 183653 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Bernard Jacobs' Speech, Jun 15, 1992; 183652 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Celebrities, Jun 15, 1992; 183651 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Commemorative Advertisements, Jun 15, 1992; 183650 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Contributions, Jun 15, 1992; 183649 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Correspondence, Jun 15, 1992; 183648 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Correspondence, "Cannot Attend", Jun 15, 1992; 183647 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Finances, Account Memos, Jun 15, 1992; 183646 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Guest List, Jun 15, 1992; 183645 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Invitation, Jun 15, 1992; 183644 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Mailing Lists, Jun 15, 1992; 183643 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Memorandum, Jun 15, 1992; 183642 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Program and Arrangements, Jun 15, 1992; 183641 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Reports, Jun 15, 1992; 183640 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Christmas Carol: Correspondence, Dec 15, 1992; 183639 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Christmas Carol: Finances, Dec 15, 1992; 183638 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Christmas Carol: Invitation, Dec 15, 1992; 183637 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Christmas Carol: Publicity, Dec 15, 1992; 183636 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Christmas Carol: Reception, Dec 15, 1992; 183635 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Christmas Carol: Reports, Dec 15, 1992; 183634 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Nothing like a Dame, Feb 26, 1996; 183633 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - For the Love of the Dove, Jun 17, 1996; 183632 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Magic and Music: Gala, Dec 16, 1996; 183631 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Stay Home: Gala, 1997; 183630 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Nothing like a Dame, Feb 24, 1997; 183629 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Lucille Lortel Awards, May 5, 1997; 183628 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - The Gin Game, 346631 (Box 24, Folder 12a)
    - Nothing like a Dame, Mar 1999; 183627 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Mr. Smith Goes to the Plaza: Gala, 2000; 183626 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Nothing like a Dame, Mar 12, 2001; 183625 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Nothing like a Dame, Mar 18, 2002; 183624 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Standing Ovation (James M. Nederlander 80th Birthday Celebration), Apr 29, 2002; 183623 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Nightingale: Poster, undated; 452433 (Box 24, Folder 17a)
    - Fundraising Updates, 2002; 556516 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1959; 183622 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1960-1962; 183621 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1963; 183620 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1964-1965; 183619 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1966-1969; 183618 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1970; 183617 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1971-1972; 183616 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1973; 183615 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1974; 183614 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1975; 183613 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1976-1977; 183612 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1978; 183611 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1991; 183610 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Subseries V:C: Bread Basket Campaigns, 1938-1980., 183479
    - Abbott, George (Bread Basket Chairman), 1978; 183608 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Act I, 1975; 183607 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Actors' Equity Association, 1968-1980; 183606 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - American Conservatory Theatre, 1965-1970; 183605 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - American Shakespeare Festival, 1965-1979; 183604 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - American Stage Festival, 1979; 183603 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Association of Theatrical Press Agents and Managers, 1968, 1980; 183602 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Barnstormers (Tamworth, NH), 1979-1980; 183601 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Berkshire Theatre Festival, 1972-1979; 183600 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Beverly Dinner Playhouse, 1974-1980; 183599 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Blood Donor Drive, 1975; 183598 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Broadway Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1963-1968; 183597 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Broadway Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1969-1972; 183596 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Broadway Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1972-1975; 183595 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Broadway Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1975-1977; 183594 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Broadway Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1977-1980; 183593 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Brunswick Music Theater, 1978; 183592 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Burstyn, Ellen and Grodin, Charles (Bread Basket Co-Chairmen), 1975; 183591 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Candlelight Dinner Playhouse, 1965-1967, 1980; 183590 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Cape Cod Melody Tent, 1979; 183589 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Cecilwood Theatre, 1966-1980; 183588 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Chanhassen Dinner Theatre, 1978; 183587 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Chicago: Actors' Fund Week, 1965; 183586 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Clippings, 1967-1968; 183585 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Collectors, undated, 1979; 183584 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Corning Summer Theater, 1965-1980; 183583 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1951; 1965, 1970; 183582 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1979; 183581 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Actors' Equity, 1971; 183580 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Dinner Theaters, 1978; 183579 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Eisenhower Theatre, 1979; 183578 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Elitch Gardens Theater, 1979-1980; 183577 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Forrest Theatre, 1979; 183576 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Gish, Lillian: Luncheon, 1978; 183575 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Gracie Mansion Reception, 1963-1979; 183574 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Great Lakes Shakespeare Festival, 1965-1980; 183573 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Grendel's Lair Cabaret Theater, 1978-1980; 183572 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Guber, Lee, 1975-1977; 183571 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Harmon, Charlotte, 1977-1978; 183570 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Hayloft Dinner Theatre, Nov 1978; 183569 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Hepburn, Katherine (Chairman, Winter Bread Basket Drive), 1969-1970; 183568 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Hippodrome Theatre, 1978; 183567 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Individual Contributors, 1975-1977; 183566 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Individual Contributors, 1978-1980; 183565 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Information Sheet on Breadbasket Drives, undated; 183564 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Ivorytown Playhouse, 1965-1972, 1979; 183563 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - John Golden Fund, 1959-1962, 1965-1975; 183562 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - John Drew Theater, 1966-1979; 183561 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Kaye, Danny, 1970-1971; 183560 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Keeler, Ruby (Bread Basket Chairman), 1971-1972; 183559 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Kenley Papers, 1978-1979; 183558 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Lakes Region Playhouse (Gilford, NH), 1979; 183557 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Lakewood Theater (Skowhegan, ME), 1965-1972, 1979; 183556 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - League of New York Theatres and Producers, 1969-1980; 183555 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Little Theater on the Square, 1965-1968; 183554 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Little Theater on the Square: Programs, 1968-1971, 1977-1978; 183553 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Master Theatre Lists, 1968, 1977-1978; 183552 (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Melody Top Theater, 1966-1980; 183551 (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Merit Awards, 1963-1964; 183550 (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Music Box Theatre, 1979; 183549 (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - New Bolton Hill Dinner Theatre, Oct 1978; 183548 (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - New Jersey Shakespeare Festival, 1972-1976, 1979-1980; 183547 (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - New Mechanic Theatre, 1979; 183546 (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Nichols, Mike (Bread Basket Chairman), 1977-1978; 183545 (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - Off-Broadway Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1965-1979; 183544 (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - Orpheum Theater, Dec 1978; 183543 (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - Out-of-Town Theatre, 1970; 183542 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Pantages Theatre, 1978; 183541 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Paramount Arts Centre, 1978; 183540 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Peterborough Players, 1964-1980; 183539 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Press Releases, 1965-1969; 183538 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Preston, Robert (Bread Basket Chairman), 1974-1975; 183537 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Procedures, 1978; 183536 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Program Inserts, 1963-1972, 1980; 183535 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Program Inserts Distribution Lists, 1965-1977; 183534 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Publicity, 1966-1968, 1975; 183533 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Publicity Expenses, 1978; 183532 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Pub Theatrical, 1974-1977; 183531 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - R. Greenspan and Co., Inc (Clipper Industries), 1965-1970; 183530 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Reeves, John, 1965-1966, 1974; 183529 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Reports, undated, 1961-1964; 183528 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Report, 1977; 183527 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Reports, 1979; 183526 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Reynolds, Debbie (Chairman), 1973-1974; 183525 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Road Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1964-1968; 183524 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Road Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1968-1975; 183523 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Road Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1980-1980; 183522 (Box 26, Folder 21)